Ahmet Buğra ÇETİNEL

Game Developer

J +90-506-334-3943 | ■ ahmetcetinel1992@gmail.com | ⊕ bugracetinel.com | In bugra-cetinel

ABOUT

Game Developer and Co-Founder of **Twenty Games** with over four years of experience. Worked on mobile game development from ideation to LiveOps, creating hit games like *Makeup Kit* (10M downloads). Integrated SDKs for analytics and monetization, and drove key decisions in gameplay systems and technical workflows.

EXPERIENCE

Twenty Games

08.2020 - Current

Game Developer, Product Owner

Ankara, Turkey

- Led the development of Makeup Kit and Pasta Fever, along with over 75 published games, managing LiveOps for several months.
- Developed a wide range of games with different mechanics and genres, and built tools to improve Unity workflows across the team.
- Worked as Product Owner for a year, overseeing the full development cycle from concept to live operations, managing a 10-person team, and streamlining collaboration with tools like ClickUp.
- Monitored and analyzed player data through A/B testing, optimizing retention and monetization strategies while enhancing game feel and gameplay balance.

Solo Developer 01.2019 - 08.2020

Ankara, Turkey

- Self-taught game development, releasing Infinity Drift, a mobile racing game.
- Developed multiple smaller projects and participated in game jams.

EDUCATION

Middle East Technical University

2010 - 2015

Bachelor's Degree of Economics

Ankara, Turkey

- GPA: 3.01 (Honor Student)
- Student Assistant of Intermediate Macroeconomics

PROJECTS

I have participated in the development of over 100 mobile games, taking on different roles for each one and learning new lessons from every project. Below, you can see a few major ones but for a complete list, please visit my website.

- Makeup Kit: 10M Downloads, reached top charts over 50 countries
- Pasta Fever: Achieved 500k+ downloads and influenced dozens of studios to adopt similar game mechanics.
- Fury Road!: \$0.11 CPI
- Morph Heroes
- Infinity Drift

SKILLS

- Programming Languages: C#, Java, Python
- Game Development Tools: Unity, Blender, Photoshop
- Project Management Tools: ClickUp, Trello, Notion
- SDKs: Facebook, Adjust, Firebase
- Version Control: Git, Plastic SCM